We'll be right back.
Frankie's past, the day the C-Train first ran.
It's too late to feign innocence.
We already know everything.
It's only a matter of time before the government targets me.
I want you to take these and leave this island, Frankie.
Tom entrusted them to Iceberg.
And Iceberg entrusted them to you.
Hey, boys, come here.
It's about time I let you in on something important.
It's been a long game, but now we're a checkmate.
See, I know you have the plans for the ancient weapon.
Hand over Pluton's blueprints, Coddy Flam.
Flam, huh?
That's kind of a funny name.
How about we just call you Frankie instead?
Whatever.
Are you listening?
Hand them over this instant.
Oh, did you just say hand...
What the hell did he just do?
It was so fast I couldn't see what happened.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Oh, my.
You found a room.
What do you suppose is this filthy place's purpose?
Those are drafting tables.
Yes, where blueprints are made.
And perhaps hidden.
Find them.
Look here.
Nameplates.
Coddy Flam.
Iceberg.
Tom.
The shipwright.
This picture.
Keep your paws off of that.
You're poking your noses into my personal space.
My memories.
This is the place where I grew up.
What used to house the shipbuilding company, Tom's workers,
were the best damn shipwright that ever lived, plied his craft.
Ah!
Thinking exist!
How is it?
Ah!
Watch out, Iceberg!
Hey, what in the hell is wrong with you?
Ow!
Idiot!
Don't you know you're not supposed to be goofing around right now?
We got real ships to work on, not your crappy toys!
Don't yell at me when you don't have a clue what you're talking about, Ice for Brains!
It isn't some crappy toy, it's my super battleship that battled Frankie!
Whatever it is, you need to leave it alone before someone gets hurt!
This is Scrap Heave Island!
I can do what I want!
Wait, you'll see!
I'm gonna build a battleship awesome enough to take down a Sea King!
Bull!
What you're gonna do is get yourself killed!
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, quick!
Nuh-uh!
Real quick!
If you wanna be a man, show some gusto!
Well, there's the old launching ceremony!
One more ship sailing with gusto!
Right, buddy?
Get him, get him, get him!
That's about enough work for today!
What do you say we head on home?
Get him, get him!
Man, I'm hungry!
Let's see what's for dinner!
Get him, get him!
Get him, get him, get him, get him!
Let's see what's for dinner!
Get him, get him!
Hey!
Hold on!
What do you say we head on home?
Dinner, dinner.
Man, I'm hungry.
Let's see what's for dinner.
Dinner, dinner.
Hey, hold on!
Wait for us!
So today's Battle Frankie model was number what are you up to?
Eight, sir.
It was really beautiful.
No, it wasn't.
Your dumb weapon that he let you build for some reason
fell apart after you almost killed both of us with it.
Nobody asked you, you stupid ice for brains.
Ice for brains?
Well, you're flunky!
All right.
That's enough fighting, boys.
Cut it out.
He started it, not me.
My word.
Don't encourage those two, Tom.
Was it that funny?
Keep laughing and they'll keep misbehaving.
Speaking of misbehaving,
I heard that another ship carrying lumber
was attacked by pirates.
I swear, ever since the king of the pirates was executed,
this place has just gone rotten with those no-good bums.
They're taking over the city.
The people's spirits are really low.
And because of all the flooding from Aqualaguna,
we can only get lumber and iron if we ship them in from other islands.
But with all the storms and pirates everywhere, it's near impossible.
The shipyards are starting to get so desperate for customers,
they are literally fighting each other for them.
So many have closed down already.
At this rate, Water 7 is on a course to sink into the ocean and fade from the world's memory.
And to think, this city made its name, making unforgettable, unsinkable ships such a shame.
Hey, you built a big super awesome pirate ship once now, didn't you, Tom?
Will you teach me how to draw out blueprints for one, too?
What's so funny, huh?
Frankie, there's no such thing as blueprints for a pirate ship.
It's the flag, boy.
Skull and bones means pirate ship.
And a seagull flag means that it's navy.
Whatever you build, just remember this.
Build it with pride.
And a whole lot of manly gusto!
You sure are working late tonight.
What are you drawing?
This here is hope for our island.
It is?
Yep.
Well, at least that's what I'm hoping that it'll turn into someday.
Now, to bed with you.
Yes, sir.
Whoa!
The judicial ship is here!
What the heck is that?
A mobile court.
I wonder who they're here for.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm not sure.
The judicial ship is here!
What the heck is that?
A mobile court.
I wonder who they're here for.
What do you think you're doing?
Let him go, you big stupid jerk.
He didn't do anything wrong!
Don't you worry!
I'll be just fine.
No, Tom!
Come back!
Justice was brought to Gold Roger, the king of the pirates,
by way of execution.
His ship, the Oro Jackson,
was built by none other than Tom,
who stands before this court today.
As penalty for aiding and abetting that vicious criminal,
Tom will be taken to Eni's lobby,
where he will be executed.
No!
The verdict was read!
Guilty!
They're gonna execute Tom!
They say it's because he built a ship for the king of the pirates.
Damn shame.
That thing brought a whole lot of grief into the world.
Now, building ships is not a crime,
and one may sell them to almost anyone who wishes to buy,
but we must make an exception for the king of the pirates.
On the charge of providing meaningful assistance to the man who terrorized the entire world,
we hereby sentence Tom to death.
Take him away!
Come on, time to go.
Move it!
You heard him!
Hurry up!
Go already!
Hey, what are you doing?
I've got a new design!
For a completely new kind of paddle steamer.
A train that will run on the surface of the ocean with gusto!
Shut up!
Get moving!
This once great island has lost its gusto.
Our trade is not what it used to be.
People have lost hope.
Water 7 is slowly sinking away.
Every day, our hard-working citizens are filled with worry.
I can lift their spirits!
I will!
By building our good people a sea train!
Quit flapping your gums and move your feet!
No, let him stay.
Sea train.
Tell me more.
It's like a ship,
but one that puffs out steam and runs on a track.
It'll go between the islands,
carrying people and all kinds of goods,
even other ships.
Most importantly,
it won't be affected by conditions at sea.
That's ridiculous!
A railway on the water will be ripped to pieces
once Aqualaguna comes around.
And even if it doesn't,
what are you gonna do about all the sea kings out there?
It doesn't have to be a completely fixed track.
Huh?
It'll be submerged under the water a bit,
so it won't be bombarded by the waves.
It'll sway, just like a rope in the water.
The sea train will just use the tracks as a guide
to get from place to place.
I'm also considering installing a mechanism
that emits a loud, dissonant sound underwater
to discourage fish from getting anywhere near the tracks.
It should work on sea kings as well,
so they won't pose a threat.
Whoa, is all that possible?
If we connect St. Poplar, Pucci, San Faldo,
and this island,
we can create a booming economy
that will help out all of us.
Amazing!
I will be finished with the blueprints very soon,
but it will take a master shipwright to build it.
Now, could this sea train run to Annie's lobby as well?
Without a doubt, Your Honor.
Once the plans are in the can
and the railway is in the water,
people can go with gusto from island to island
for work or play.
And once again,
Water 7 will be a city filled with hope!
How long will it take?
Ten years.
Then build it.
If you agree to develop this sea train,
I will give you the time to do it.
Consider these next ten years as probation.
That's great news!
Good luck, Tom!
Save Water 7, please!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Ah, gusto!
I'm alive!
I'm glad you think this is so funny.
I thought you were a goner.
I was worried sick over you.
But I guess if this plan of yours works out,
they're willing to forgive and forget
the whole Gold Roger affair.
Well, I just gotta tell you
how amazed I am with you, Tom.
What a great idea!
It's unbelievable!
To think you could just come up with that on your own,
it's brilliant when you told...
Thanks for the grub.
Come on, Yokozuna.
I'll teach you the front crawl.
Yeah.
Hey, we're all celebrating here
and you wanna leave?
What's your deal?
My deal?
What happened to Tom was so unfair!
He built the only ship
that was able to sail the whole Grand Line,
something no one else in the world could do!
And those jerks wanna put him to death over it?
They don't realize how hard that is!
They couldn't even string together a raft
if their lives depended on it!
I mean, I know that the whole reason
our office is under this bridge
is cause those stupid people
kicked you out of town over that ship!
You're the greatest shipbuilder
the world has ever known
and they treat you like garbage!
What are you laughing at,
you big yellow weirdo?
You're crazy!
Stop attacking him, you stupid kid!
Why does he have to laugh at everything?
No, no, no!
You're doing it wrong!
Stroke harder and push that water back!
Get it!
No, no!
Do it harder!
Don't hold back!
That Frankie's got a lot of nerve!
If I were you,
I'd kick him out for what he just did!
Well, I know the boy can be a handful,
but he's a fellowship mill-
夢見た僕らは間違いじゃないと信じて 荒く埋れる海原を渡って行ける
誰よりも勇敢で思いやりもあるけれど
もしも君がこの船を降りて 違う世界にいたとしても
最後にはきっと笑えるよ
お直ホームをめるべきなら トムに 得るbumを誇る
光がーみんなだよ
それはトムに強くていない
このシアトレートを双手で彼に閉じる
チャージが多そうですね
その講義では本強してことがたくばしい
誰よりも鍵をしてお適合させuko
やり回り担い死に
麦の巨装を出してくれる
ラ Um 下ienのウがいまさい